fujitv.live 2017-11-19

# FUJITV - Privacy Policy

We respects your privacy very much. We wish to ensure your shopping experience safe, convenient and care-free.Please take a moment reading the following content in detail.

Persional Information  
We will ask you to provide personal information(including name,email address, phone number,etc.)when you want to get service from our website. We will treat your personal information carefully and guarantee that we never sell or rent your personal information.The only purpose to collect users’ personal information is for provide better service.

About cookies  
[FUJITV](http://fujitv.live/fujitv) requries brower to enable cookie to work properly.We use cookies(A cookie is a small text file that a Website writes to your hard drive)for better understand what services are valuable to our customers.They cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses.

3rd party credit card processors  
We use security server hosted by other 3rd party credit card processors and encrypt all your personal information including your name, address, credit card number, credit card expiration date,This can prevent any malicious use of your personal information and make sure it is only used for online transition.

Your Choices  
If you have any query please email to our customer service and we will respond to your via Email as soon as possible.

Statement updated  
Statement will be updated on our site, so please visit this page periodically to ensure that you have made it clear about our latest privacy statement.
